I: What did you do last weekend?
S: Last weekend it was my birthday, so I went out for a meal with friends,
and it was very sunny as well, so we went for a long walk afterwards.
I: Where did you go for your last holiday?
J: I went to Japan for Christmas.
I: When was the last time you went to a restaurant?
R: The last time I went to a restaurant, er,
was over the weekend.
I went to Sweetwater, in, er,
it’s a French restaurant in Brooklyn.
I: Did you enjoy the meal?
R: I loved it. It was great.
I: Are you good at giving directions?
C: No, I’m not.
I am the worst person to ask for directions.
I myself am not good at finding places or following directions,
so I pretty much am not good at it.
I: Is there a good café near here?
S: Yes, there is. It’s just along on the right.